Friedman, Clara Arbitration Files 5770
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Clara Friedman Arbitration Files
1975-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Friedman, Clara
5770
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Case files, collective labor agreements, records (documents).
Collective labor agreements
3124289
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 20, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5251: New York City Mayor's Advisory Transit Committee Hearing Transcripts and Records
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Friedman, Clara H.; Civil Service Employees Association (N.Y.); General Motors Corporation; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers; Pan American World Airways, Inc.; New York (State). Department of Mental Hygiene
3124289
- ADELPHI UNIVERSITY/SEIU, AAA 1730-0173-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Calculation of Overtime Award October 12th
- AMERICAN BANK NOTE/GRAPKIC ARTS, AAA 1330-0060-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Discharge of J. Friedman, Award March 5th
- BETH ISRAEL MEDICAL CENTER/DISTRICT 1199, AAA 1330-1443-77, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Discharge of C. Quinones, Award January 23rd
- BOULDER (CITY OF)/PBA, AAA 7139-0213-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Discharge of J. Andrews, October 7th
- BUTLER AVIATION/TEAMSTERS, FMCS 75K16579, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Layoffs, etc. Agreement reached November 25th
- CARLE PLACE SCHOOL DISTRICT/TEACHERS, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  PERB Fact-Finding, Report January 13th
- CARLE PLACE SCHOOL DISTRICT/ADMINISTRATORS, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  PERB Fact-Finding, Report May 31st
- COMMUNITY HOSPITAL OF BROOKLYN/DISTRICT 1199, AAA 1330-0710-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Benefit Funds, Stipulation August 5th
- COMSEWOGUE SCHOOL DISTRICT/TEACHERS, AAA 1339-1373-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Reassignment, Award February 11th
- CONSUMERS UNION/NEWSPAPER GUILD, Denial of bumping, AAA 1330-1569-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Award July 8th
- CULINARY INSTITUTE/SEIU, Local 74, NYSMB A80-1248, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Discharge of S. Shubosky, Award November 13th
- DANNON MILK/TEAMSTERS LOCAL 584, AAA 1330-0808-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Attendance Control Plan, Award September 22th
- DEAN PRODUCTS/ TEAMSTERS LOCAL 810, AAA 1330-1173-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Vacation, of C. Carter, Award November 30th
- EASTMOUNT/MARINE ENGINEERS, Contributions to MEBA Benefit Plans, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Award January 20th
- FLOWER & FIFTH AVENUE HOSPITALS/DISTRICT 119 9, Change of Wage Payment-Period, AAA 1330-0628-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Award January 17th
- FORMS TRUCKING/TEAMSTERS LOCAL 282, AAA 1730-0255-81, Reinstatement of J. Edwards, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  October 6th, Award
- GENERAL MOTORS, PLANT GUARDS LOCAL 64, Appeal Case A-10, Termination of Security Officer, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  December 19th; Award
- GENERAL MOTORS/IUERM, Appeal Case M-4281, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Discharge of A.D.C. Award
- GENERAL MOTORS, IUERM, Umpire Case N-5, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Shift Entitlement, Award April 8th
- GENERAL MOTORS/IUERM, Appeal Case N-309, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Reinstatement, Award March 19th
- GENERAL MOTORS/IUERM, Appeal Case N-24, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Discharge, Award October 30th
- GENERAL MOTORS/IUERM, Appeal Case N-4085, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Discharge, Award November 14th
- GREAT NECK SCHOOL DISTRICT/ADULT EDUCATION TEACHERS, PERB M76-618, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Fact-Finder's Report October 15th
- GREAT NECK SCHOOL DISTRICT/BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS EMPLOYEES, PERBM76-223, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Fact-Finder's Report October 6th
- GRISTEDE/TEAMSTERS LOCAL 202, AAA 1330-0398-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Holiday Pay, Award July 21st
- HARLEM HOSPITAL/DOCTORS, AAA 1330-1352-79, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Termination of N. Weekes, Award March 19th
- HARLEM HOSPITAL/DISTRICT 1199, AAA1330-1000-78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Discharge of J. Tyson, Award November 11th
- HAUPPAGE SCHOOLS/OFFICE STAFF, PERB M81-292, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Fact-Finder's Report October 16th
- HAUPPAGE SCHOOLS/SEIU, LOCAL 144, PERB M81-276 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- HEMPSTEAD SCHOOLS/TEACHERS, AAA 1739-0196-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Evaluation of L. Bembry, Award January 20th
- HERRICKS SCHOOLS/ADMINISTRATORS AND SUPERVISORS, AAA 1739-0090-78, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Per Diem Pay, Award March 8th
- ITT/CWA, LOCAL 1172, AAA 1330-0961-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Assignment wage-rate, Award April 22nd
- JERSEY CITY BOARD OF EDUCATION/TEACHERS, PERC AR-79-214, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Stipend for Remedial Reading Teachers, Sward June 13th
- JEWISH HOME FOR AGED/DISTRICT 1199, AAA 1330-1894-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Night Shift Differential, Award April 4th
- KINGS PARK SCHOOL DISTRICT/CSEA, AAA 1339-1157-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Anniversary Date, Award December 20th
- LACKAWANNA CITY SCHOOL DISTRICT/CSEA, PERB A80-203, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Bumping down, Award April 10th
- LAKELAND SCHOOL DISTRICT/AFT, PERB M76-216, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Fact-Finder Report July 16th
- LEGAL AID SOCIETY/ATTORNEYS, AAA 1330-1765-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Suspension of H. Meyerson, Award March 8th
- LINDENHURST BOARD OF EDUCATION/TEACHERS, Grievances of P. Quinn, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Award Oct. 25th
- LLOYD HARBOR/PBA, PERB A76-135, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Tours of Duty and Vacations, Award September 28th
- MAIMONIDES/DISTRICT 1199, AAA 1330-0685-78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Termination of D. Green, Award October 14th
- MALLON, PETER F./GRAPHIC ARTS, Vacation Credits, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Award Oct. 27th
- METROPOLITAN MUSEUM OF ART/AFSCME, AAA 1330-0851-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Discharge of J. Gill Award Oct. 19th
- MOUNT SINAI HOSPITAL/DISTRICT 1199, AAA 1330-0908-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Termination of A. Nicholson, Award Oct. 15th
- NANUET SCHOOL DISTRICT/CSEA, PERB M75-746, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Fact-Finder's Report Nov. 28th
- NEW JERSEY TRANSPORTATION DEPARTMENT/LOCAL 195, IFPTE, OER-201, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  Discipline of R. Kiederling, Award Nov. 16th
- NYC FINANCE DEPARTMENT/DC 37, OCB A-7 3 0-7 8, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Wage Rate, Award July 10th
- NYC HEALTH AND HOSPITALS/SSEU, LOCAL 371, OCB A-1232-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Discharge of I. Brummer, Award June 1st
- NYS CORRECTION DEPARTMENT/CSEA, Fact-Finder Report, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  May 14th
- NYS CORRECTION (ARTHUR KILD/M. STATON, GRIEVANT, AAA 13671-0016-78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  Termination of M. Staton, Award December 22nd
- NYS CORRECTION (ARTHUR KILL)/COUNCIL 82 AFSCME, AAA 13671-0040-78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Discipline of P. DeGaetano, Award Oct. 16th
- NYS CORRECTION (EDGECOMBE)/COUNCIL 82 AFSCME, AAA 13671 0001-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  Discipline of R. Russell, Award February 8th
- NYS CORRECTION/COUNCIL 82 AFSCME, AAA 13671-0053-78, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  Dismissal of J. Wynn, Award Jan. 15th
- NYS CORRECTION/COUNCIL 82 AFSCME, AAA 13671-0023-79, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  Discipline of J. Bethea, Award August 31st
- NYS DRUG ABUSE COMMISSION/CSEA, AAA 1367-0075-75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  Grievance of R. Jacobson, Award September 26th
- NYS HEALTH (HELEN HAYES HOSPITAL)/ COUNCIL 82 AFSCME, AAA 1367-0007-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  Termination of M. Lyman, Award April 10th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (BROOKLYN DEVELOPMENTAL CENTER)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0323-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  Termination of V. Evans, Award February 2nd
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (BROOKLYN DEVELOPMENTAL CENTER)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0213-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  Termination of Grievant, Award October 14th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (CENTRAL ISLIP)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0262-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  Termination of T. Demery, Award October 28th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (CENTRAL ISLIP]_/CSEA, AAA 1367-0220-&0221-75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  Terminations of I. Johnson and M. Carty, Award February 4th
- NYS MENTAL HEALTH (CREEDMOOR)/COUNCIL 82 AFSCME, AAA 13671-0039-79, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  Discharge of F. Newton, Award November 1st
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (CREEDMOOR)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0353-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  Suspension of R. Staley, Award March 1st
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (CREEDMOOR)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0120-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  Suspension of J. Kelly, Award May 31st
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (KINGSBORO)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0200-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  Discipline of K. Johnson, Award September 30th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (KINGS PARK)/CSEA AAA 1367-0370-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  Termination of J. Clancy, Award January 12th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (LETCHWORTH)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0135-75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  Termination of J. Turner, Award December 16th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (PILGRIM PSYCHIATRIC CENTER)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0036-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  Termination of S. Elefterion, Award February 24th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (PILGRIM)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0085-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  Termination of Juan Castro, Award April 6th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (PILGRIM)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0078-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  Suspension of J. Oalden, Award April 16th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (PILGRIM)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0215 &0216&0217-75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  Terminations of 0.Gentry, M. Broderick, C. Gaines, Award February 3rd
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (PILGRIM)/CSEA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  Posting of Exam, Award November 18th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (QUEENS)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0020-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  Discipline of F. Alexander, R. Alexander, February 3rd
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (ROCKLAND)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0152-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  Discipline of R. Williams, Award June 21st
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (ROCKLAND)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0052-75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  Discipline of S. Remick, Award August 14th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (WASSAIC)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0034-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  Discipline of E. Wright, Award March 3rd
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (WASSAIC)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0012-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  Discipline of P. Williams, Award March 8th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (WILLOWBROOK)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0136-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  Discipline of R. Cummings, Award June 8th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (WILLOWBROOK)/CSEA, AAA 1367-185-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  Discipline of G. Hanulak, Award August 4th
- NYS MENTAL HYG IENE(WILLOWBROOK)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0025-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  Discipline of J. King, Award March 10th
- NYS MENTAL HYGIENE (WILLOWBROOK)/CSEA, AAA 1367-0120-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  Discipline of M. Scott, Award May 24th
- NYS PARKS (ROBERTO CLEMENTE PARK)/ COUNCIL 82, AFSCME, AAA 13671-0029-79, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  Discipline of J. Aponte, Award August 31st
- NY TELEPHONE/CWA, TELCO FILE A-75-82, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  Suspension of B. Zaino, Award January 18th
- OCEANSIDE SCHOOL DISTRICT/TEACHERS, PERB M76-131, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  Fact-Finder's Report September 2nd
- OVERSEAS NATIONAL AIRWAYS/TEAMSTERS LOCAL 851, AAA 1330-1403-77, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  Layoff, Award April 26th
- PAN AM/TWU (H. Bandison), COM-79-4-JFK, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  Award August 11th
- PAN AM/TWU LOCAL 504, M-80-272-JFK, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  Discharge of Malitch, Award June 8th
- PAN AM/TEAMSTERS, C-78-117-HO, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  Discharge of S.S.L. Lo, Award June 7th
- PLAINFIELD BOARD OF EDUCATION/TEACHERS, AAA 1839-0269-75D, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  Salary Placement, Award September 16th
- POUGHKEEPSIE (CITY OF)/CSEA, AAA 1330-0699-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  Discipline of C. Abbott, Award June 27th
- PRATT INSTITUTE/AFT, AAA 1330-0956-78, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  Tenure of R. Borichewski, Award January 29th
- PRINTERS LITHOGRAPHING/GRAPHIC ARTS, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  Discharge of J. Hacker, Award November 12th
- REVERE SMELTING/TEAMSTERS LOCAL 707, AAA 1330-1120-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  Discharge of W. Spafford, Award October 2nd
- ROCKLAND COUNTY/CSEA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  Safety Shoes, Award July 2nd
- ROCKLAND COUNTY/CSEA (B. Powell), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  Award December 14th
- ROSLYN SCHOOL DISTRICT/CUSTODIAL,BUS,MAINTENACE, PERB M75-376, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  Fact-Finder Report July 18th
- ROSLYN SCHOOL DISTRICT/ADMINISTRATORS AND SUPERVISORS, PERB M75-358, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  Fact-Finder Report, July 23rd
- ROSLYN SCHOOL DISTRICT/SECRETARIES, PERB 75-125, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  Fact-Finder Report July 17th
- RYDER TRUCK RENTAL, IAM LOCAL 447, AAA 1330-0572-82, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  Discharge of E. Balla, Award July 22nd
- SCHENECTADY (CITY OF)/PBA, PERB A 78-288, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  Tour Assignments, Award May 4th
- SELFHELP COMMUNITY SERVICES/DISTRICT COUNCIL 1707, AFSCME, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  Vacation and Sick Pay, Award January 12th
- SINGER, BARRY/EQUITY-LEAGUE WELFARE AND PENSION TRUST FUNDS, AAA 1330-0217-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  Required Contributions, Award June 23rd
- SOUTHSIDE HOSP./DISTR.1199 (J. Pasquerella) AAA1730-0233-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  Award July 27th
- SUFFOLK COUNTY BOCES/ADMINISTRATIVE AND SUPERVISORY ASSOCIATION, PERB M79-113, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  Fact-Finder Report October 30th
- TRANSPORT OF NEW JERSEY/AMALGAMATED TRANSIT UNION, NJSMB 80-589, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  Work Assignment, Award May 22nd
- ULSTER COUNTY LEGISLATURE/CSEA, AAA 1339-0811-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  Work Transfer, Award December 12th
- UNITY HOSPITAL/DISTRICT 1199, AAA 1330-0168-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  Grievance of Colleen Davis, Award May 4th
- U.S. HEW/AFGE LOCAL 2369, FMCS 77K16367, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  Job Change, Award December 24th
- U.S. HEW/AFGE LOCAL 3369, FMCS 77K20450, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  Documents in Employee File, Award December 6th
- U.S.MILITARY TRAFFIC MANAGEMENT/AFGE LOCAL 2855, FMCS 80K-19926, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  Removal of J. Kachmar, Award October 14th
- WHITE PLAINS (CITY OF)/LOCAL 45 6, SANITATION AND INCINERATOR WORKERS, AAA 1339-1748-75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  Holiday Pay, Award May 17th
- WILTWYCK SCHOOL/DISTRICT COUNCIL 1707 AFSCME, AAA 1330-1436-77, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  Seniority in Layoff, Award May 17th
- YONKERS (CITY OF)/FIRE FIGHTERS, PERB M75-914, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  Award May 24th
- YONKERS (CITY OF)/PBA, PERB M75-680, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  Interest Arbitration, Award April 28th
- A & P/IBT (Handley Discharge) AAA 1330-1395-83, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Stipulation
- ADELPHI UNIV./AAUP (Box 2, Folder 2)
  transcripts and papers on a case that was settled during hearings; no award issued.
- ALLEGHENY CTY.SAN.AUTH./UTILITY WKRS AAA 55-39-0152-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Award November 10th
- AMERICAN BOOK/GRAPHIC ARTS(J. Cameron) AAA1330-0347-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Award June 9th
- AMSTAR/ILA (H. Stozek) AAA 1330-1046-80, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Award December 19th
- Bloomingdales/STORRWORKERS (R. Dispirito) AAA 1330-1110-85 Withdraw., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  December
- BOAR'S HEAD/BUTCHER. NYSMB A78-156, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Award June 19th
- BOWNE/PRESSMEN (Web Press), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Award February 2nd
- BRINK'S/I-B.T., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Award March 9th
- BRONX-LEBANON HOSP. URSES (S. Gallousis) AAA 1330-1357-81, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Award March 18th
- BROOKLYN HOSPITAL Award 144 (Longevity, vacation) AAA 1330-0604-82 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- GARBER POLLACK/GRAPHIC ARTS (Holiday Pay), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Award June 2nd
- HATCO PRINTING/GRAPHIC ARTS (M. Slattery), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Award May 16th
- LEAR SEIGLER/IUE (Layoff) AAA 1330-0109-83, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Award May 10th
- MHD/IBT (D. DiGiacomo) AAA 1330-0653-83, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Award September 30th
- MT. SINAI SCHOOLS/TEACHERS (Prep, periods) AAA 1739-0014-82, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Award April 8th
- COMSEWOGUE BD. OF ED/TECHERS (Excess students) AAA 1739-0324-81 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- DONNO/IBT (W. Lee) NYSMB A81-2042, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Award April 14th
- EINSTEIN (ALBERT) COLLEGE OF MEDICINE/MAINTENANCE & CRAFTSMEN S,Ca0tiglione) AAA 1330-1031-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Award November 17th
- ELWOOD SCHOOLS/SECYS (Ammirato) AAA 1739-0390-81, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Award April 23rd
- EXECUTIVE/IUE (McKissick) AAA 1330-0690-80, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Award May 30th
- FRIENDS CROWN HTS. DAY CARE/DC 1707 AAA 1339-1594-77, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Award June 30th
- KEYSTONE CARBON/IUE (Maternity Benefits) AAA 55-30-0124-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Award November 3rd
- LA GUARDIA HOSPITAL/NURSES AAA 1330-1537-80, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Award September 21st
- LEDERLE LABS/CHEMICAL WKRS (Overtime) FMCS 82K/12514, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Award August 12th
- LINDENHURST SCHOOLS/ADMINISTRATORS PERB M80-343, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Fact-Finding Report February 12th
- LEXINGTON SCHOOLS/TEACHERS (L. Fredericks) AAA1330-0812-81, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Award November 7th
- LINDENHURST SCHOOLS/TEACHERS, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Award March 7th
- LILCO/IBEW (Jobsites) AAA 1730-0136-81, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Award April 19th
- LILCO/IBEW (Provenzano suspension) AAA 1730-0137-81, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Award February 9th
- MALLON/GRAPHIC ARTS (Overtime), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Award May 21st
- MASBACK/IBT L.202 (W. Credell) AAA 1330-0858-82, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Award December 12th
- MT.SINAI HOSPITAL/DISTR.1199 (J. Martinez) AAA 1330-0194-80, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- MT.SINAI HOSPITAL/DISTR.1199 (C. Cheatham) AAA 1330-0551-78, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Award February 7th
- NENA/DISTRICT 1199 (Vasquez) AAA 1330-0665-82, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Award April 15th
- NEW ENGLAND TELEPHONE/IBEW (Licausi) AAA1130-2044-83, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Award October 29th
- NYC BD OF ED/CSA (R.FUCHS) AAA 1339-0391-81, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Award
- NYC HEALTH & HOSPITALS/DC 37 (I. Flowers) OCB A-1557-82, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- NYC HEALTH & HOSP/IBT (G. Johns) OCB A-1196-81, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NYC HEALTH & HOSP/SSEU (K. Pawlowski) OCB A-1279-81, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- NY TELEPHONE/CWA (T.I.) Telco A-82-53, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- NYS CORRECTIONS/LINDNER,JONES, POIRIER AAA 13671-0020-77, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- NYS CORRECTIONS/CLEMENT (Section 75 Proceedings) Report & Recom, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- NYU MEDICAL CENTER/IBT,L.510 (Suspension), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Award April 18th
- OZARK AIRLINES/ALPA (Lentz, King), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Award April 17th
- PAN AM/FLT ATTENDANTS (S. Axelson), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Award April 30th
- PAN AM/IBT,L.757 (Rinaldi), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Award May 23rd
- PAN AM/IBT, L.732 (Tejeda), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Award Oct. 23rd
- PAN AM/TWU (Wright), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Award June 24th
- PAN AM/IBT, L.732 (Longo), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Award Feb. 3rd
- PAN AM/TWU (Work assignment), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Award June 29th
- PAN AM/TWU (Hudson), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Award March 11th
- PAN AM/TWU (Gross), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Award Jan. 18th
- PAN AM/FRANK GICK (LPP of Merger), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Award Jan. 9th
- PATH/CARMEN (Presidential Emergency Board 193, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Report May 12th
- PEPSI-COLA/TEAMSTERS (Avant) NJSMB 82-1063, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Award Jan. 23rd
- PWT/ILA (Funds) AAA1330-1510-81, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Award Feb. 24th
- RADIO CITY/AFGVA (Tour cancellation) AAA 1330-0444-83, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Award Sept. 9th
- RANDOLPH ED. FUND/D.C.1707 (WILLIAMS) AAA 1330-0727-80, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Award July 29th
- ROCHDALE VILLAGE/LOCAL 32B (Lopez) AAA 1330-1504-82, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Award April 1st
- ROCKLAND CTY./CSEA Shift Differential, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Settlement Oct. 8th
- ROCKVILLE CENTER/CSEA PERB M83-52 9, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Settlement Apr. 6th
- RUTGERS/AAUP (Simone, Goldner) NJSMB 82-4 6 7, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Award May 18th
- SACHEM SCHOOLS/OFFICE STAFF PERB M84-34, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Fact-finding settlement Nov. 9th
- SAYVILLE SCHOOLS/CSEA PERB M80-287, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Fact-finding settlement Nov. 14th
- U.S.IMM.& NAT./AFGE fmcs 81K-10274, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Award Aug. 19th
- U.S.IMM.& NAT./AFGE (Yusaf) FMCS 82K/11846, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Award Oct. 22nd
- U.S.SOC.SEC./AFGE (W. White) FMCS 81K/08861, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Award May 26th
- U.S.VA/AFGE (Rios) FMCS 84K/18478, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Award January 8th
- U.S.ARMY/AFGE (Levinson) FMCS 82K/02281, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Award Oct. 8th
- VALLEY STREAM SCHOOLS/LOCAL 144 PERB M79-329, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Fact-Finder Report Oct. 30th
- VITELCO/USA(Richards) FMCS 82K/30301, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Award March 31st
- WATERVLIET/PBA (Interest Arbitration) PERB IA82-18, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Award March 28th